

VICTOR IHUOMA

CONTACT

+45 5290 4943

ucihu17@student.sdu.dk

B.S Ingemannsvej 2,6400 Sønderborg,Denmark.

References:

Norbert Hanigovski Project manager Danfoss norbert@danfoss.com

Dr. Jost Adam
Associate Professor NanoSYD,
Mads Clausen Institute,
University Of Southern Denmark
jostadam@mci.sdu.dk

PROFILE

A highly detailed and disciplined Mechatronic Engineer with experience across diverse engineering disciplines and project levels. Proficient in Engineering product designs and solutions, Machine learning and Data Analysis. My core skills include but are not limited to Modelling and Control engineering, Data Analysis and Machine learning applications.

EXPERIENCE

ACADEMIC SUPERVISOR

SDU NANOSYD MCI (SDU.DK) | FEB 2018 - PRESENT

- Performed Control simulations using Matlab Simulink and python
- Performed Data Visualisation and Analysis using Plotly and python

CONDITION MONITORING INTERN (IN-COMPANY PERIOD)

DANFOSS DRIVES (DANFOSS.COM)| SEP 2018 - PRESENT

- Build set-up with smart sensor for vibration measurement in variable speed drive application.
- Establish Danfoss IoT cloud connectivity.
- Perform evaluation and analysis of data collected from the sensor correlated with drive signals.
- Investigate Supervised and Unsupervised Machine learning algorithms for condition monitoring.

MECHANICAL ENGINEERING INTERN

SHELL (SHELL.COM)| AUG 2014 - APR 2015

- Research, development and testing of rotating mechanical parts.
- Developed and reviewed technical reports.
- Undertook Process optimization training.

EDUCATION

MSc. Mechatronics Engineering
UNIVERSITY OF SOUTHERN DENMARK | 2017 - 2019

B.Eng. Mechanical Engineering

UNIVERSITY OF PORT-HARCOURT | 2016

GPA: 4.15/5.0

SKILLS

- MATLAB & SIMULINK
- COMSOL
- AUTOCAD
- ANSYS
- MICROSOFT POWER BI
- Git

- PYTHON
- NODEJs
- Spark
- MCT10
- C++
- R

PROJECTS

OPTIMAL EVAPORATING AND CONDENSING TEMPERATURES OF ORGANIC RANKINE CYCLE IN A HOT AND HUMID ENVIRONMENT

CATEGORY: THERMODYNAMICS

2016

MODELLING AND OPTIMIZATION OF DIELECTRIC ELASTOMERS

CATEGORY: MODELLING

2018

CORRELATION VS CAUSATION (TRANSIT SERVICES IN POOR WEATHER CONDITIONS)

CATEGORY: DATA ANALYSIS

2018

MODIFICATION & CONTROL OF CNC MACHINE

CATEGORY: CONTROL ENGINEERING

2018

PERFORMANCE EVALUATION & DATA ANALYSIS USING SMART SENSORS

CATEGORY: DATA ANALYSIS & VISUALIZATION

2018

ANOMALY DETECTION IN HVAC SYSTEMS USING FISVDD

CATEGORY: MACHINE LEARNING & IOT (MASTER THESIS)

2018

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

LEVEL: MOTHER TONGUE

DANISH

LEVEL: INTERMEDIATE

GERMAN

LEVEL: BEGINNER